database = [
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word:The trouble in the Middle East has a serious (affect, effect) over the world.',
        optionA: 'Affect',
        optionB: 'Effect',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The (brakes, breaks) on my car don’t work properly.',
        optionA: 'Brakes',
        optionB: 'Breaks',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The (principal, principle) of our school gave an interesting lecture today.',
        optionA: 'Principal',
        optionB: 'Principle',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: (There, their) are several summer jobs available for students our age.',
        optionA: 'There',
        optionB: 'Their',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The committee cast (its, it’s) vote in favour of the new law.',
        optionA: "It's",
        optionB: 'Its',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Facetious’ is:',
        optionA: 'Humorous; not meant to be serious',
        optionB: 'The condition of being impeded or stopped',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Gullible’ is:',
        optionA: 'Radiating light; glowing',
        optionB: 'Easily taken advantage of or deceived; naive',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Hindrance’ is:',
        optionA: 'The condition of being impeded or stopped',
        optionB: 'The authority to interpret the law and administer justice.',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Jurisdiction’ is:',
        optionA: 'A person who gives an oral translation between people speaking different languages',
        optionB: 'The authority to interpret the law and administer justice.',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Luminous’ is:',
        optionA: 'A person who gives an oral translation between people speaking different languages',
        optionB: 'Radiating light; glowing',
        answer: 'B'
    }
]